<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Create Endpoint ssmmessages :: My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.2-endpointssmmessages/index.html</link>
    <description>Create VPC Endpoint SSMMESSAGES Go to VPC service management console Click Endpoints. Click Create endpoint. At the Create endpoint page. In the Name tag field, enter SSMMESSAGES. In the Service Category section, select AWS Services. In the Service Name section, In the Service category select: AWS services In the Service Name field enter: ssmmessages then select Service Name: com.amazonaws.ap-southeast-1.ssmmessages. In the Service Name column, click com.amazonaws.ap-southeast-1.ssmmessages. In the VPC section, select Lab VPC. Select the first AZ, then select the Lab Private Subnet subnet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.2-endpointssmmessages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tạo Endpoint ssmmessages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.2-endpointssmmessages/_index.vi/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.2-endpointssmmessages/_index.vi/index.html</guid>
      <description>Tạo VPC Endpoint SSMMESSAGES Truy cập đến giao diện quản trị của dịch vụ VPC Click Endpoints. Click Create endpoint. Tại trang Create endpoint. Tại mục Name tag điền SSMMESSAGES. Tại mục Service Category chọn AWS Services. Tại mục Service Name, Tại mục Service category chọn: AWS services Tại mục Service Name nhập: ssmmessages sau đó chọn Service Name: com.amazonaws.ap-southeast-1.ssmmessages. Tại cột Service Name, click chọn com.amazonaws.ap-southeast-1.ssmmessages. Tại mục VPC, chọn Lab VPC. Chọn AZ đầu tiên, sau đó chọn subnet Lab Private Subnet.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>