<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Connect to EC2 servers :: My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/index.html</link>
    <description>In this step, we will connect to our EC2 servers, located in both the public and private subnets.&#xA;Content 3.1. Connect to EC2 Public Server 3.2. Cconnect to EC2 Private Server</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connect to Public Instance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.1-public-instance/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.1-public-instance/index.html</guid>
      <description>Go to EC2 service management console. Click on Public Linux Instance. Click Actions. Click Security. Click Modify IAM role. At the Modify IAM role page. Click to select SSM-Role. Click Save. Note You will need to wait about 10 minutes before performing the next step. This time our EC2 instance will automatically register with the Session Manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect to Private instance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/index.html</guid>
      <description>For Windows instance located in private subnet, there is no public IP, no internet gateway so it cannot go out internet.&#xA;With this type of instance, the traditional way is to use Bastion host technique which is expensive and laborious, but here we will use Session Manager with this type.&#xA;Basically, the private instance still has to open the TCP 443 port to System Manager, but we don’t want to allow connection go out to the internet, but only in its VPC, to enhance our security posture.&#xA;To do that, we have to include the System Manager endpoint in the VPC, that is, using the VPC interface endpoint:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tạo kết nối đến máy chủ EC2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/_index.vi/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/_index.vi/index.html</guid>
      <description>Trong bước này, chúng ta sẽ thực hiện tạo kết nối đến các máy chủ EC2 của chúng ta, nằm trong cả public và private subnet.&#xA;Nội dung 3.1. Tạo Kết nối đến máy chủ EC2 Public 3.2. Tạo Kết nối đến máy chủ EC2 Private</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>