<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Example Content :: My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/index.html</link>
    <description>Example content from Admin of FCJ&#xA;Overall In this lab, you’ll learn the basics and practice of Amazon System Manager - Session Manager . Perform creating public and private instance connections.&#xA;Content Introduction Preparation Connect to EC2 instance Manage session logs Port Forwarding Clean up resources</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 08:33:42 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1414/example-content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/1-introduce/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/1-introduce/index.html</guid>
      <description>Session Manager is a function within the AWS System Manager service, SSM provides verifiable and secure version management without opening incoming ports, without Bastion Host or SSH key management. Session Manager also makes it easy to comply with corporate policies that require controlled access to instances, strict security practices, and fully auditable logs with instance access details, while still providing end-users with one-click cross-platform access to your managed instances.&#xA;By using Session Manager, you get the following advantages that traditional methods do not have:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preparation </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/2-prerequiste/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/2-prerequiste/index.html</guid>
      <description>Info You need to create 1 Linux instance on the public subnet and 1 Window instance on the private subnet to perform this lab.&#xA;To learn how to create EC2 instances and VPCs with public/private subnets, you can refer to the lab:&#xA;About Amazon EC2 Works with Amazon VPC In order to use System Manager to manage our window instances in particular and our instances in general on AWS, we need to give permission to our instances to be able to work with System Manager. In this preparation, we will also proceed to create an IAM Role to grant permissions to instances that can work with System Manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect to EC2 servers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/index.html</guid>
      <description>In this step, we will connect to our EC2 servers, located in both the public and private subnets.&#xA;Content 3.1. Connect to EC2 Public Server 3.2. Cconnect to EC2 Private Server</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage session logs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/4-s3log/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/4-s3log/index.html</guid>
      <description>With Session Manager, we can view the history of connections to instances through Session history. However, we have not seen the details of the commands used in a session.&#xA;In this section, we will proceed to create an S3 bucket and configure the session logs feature to see the details of the commands used in the session.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Port Forwarding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/5-portfwd/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/5-portfwd/index.html</guid>
      <description>Info Port Forwarding is a useful way to redirect network traffic from one IP address - Port to another IP address - Port. With Port Forwarding we can access an EC2 instance located in the private subnet from our workstation.&#xA;We will configure Port Forwarding for the RDP connection between our machine and Private Windows Instance located in the private subnet we created for this exercise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean up resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/6-cleanup/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 08:33:42 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/6-cleanup/index.html</guid>
      <description>We will take the following steps to delete the resources we created in this exercise.&#xA;Delete EC2 instance Go to EC2 service management console&#xA;Click Instances. Select both Public Linux Instance and Private Windows Instance instances. Click Instance state. Click Terminate instance, then click Terminate to confirm. Go to IAM service management console&#xA;Click Roles. In the search box, enter SSM. Click to select SSM-Role. Click Delete, then enter the role name SSM-Role and click Delete to delete the role.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>