<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Create VPC Endpoint :: My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/index.html</link>
    <description>Create VPC Endpoint SSM We will create 3 interface endpoints required by the Session Manager:&#xA;Interface endpoints: com.amazonaws.region.ssm com.amazonaws.region.ec2messages com.amazonaws.region.ssmmessages You can refer to more here&#xA;Content: Create Endpoint ssm Create Endpoint ssmmessages Create Endpoint ec2messages</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create Endpoint ssm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.1-endpointssm/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.1-endpointssm/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create VPC Endpoint SSM Go to VPC service management console Click Endpoints. Click Create endpoint. At the Create endpoint page. In the Name tag field, enter SSM. In the Service Category section, select AWS Services. In the Service Name section, In the Service category section, select: AWS services In the Service Name section enter: SSM then select Service Name: com.amazonaws.ap-southeast-1.ssm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Endpoint ssmmessages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.2-endpointssmmessages/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.2-endpointssmmessages/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create VPC Endpoint SSMMESSAGES Go to VPC service management console Click Endpoints. Click Create endpoint. At the Create endpoint page. In the Name tag field, enter SSMMESSAGES. In the Service Category section, select AWS Services. In the Service Name section, In the Service category select: AWS services In the Service Name field enter: ssmmessages then select Service Name: com.amazonaws.ap-southeast-1.ssmmessages. In the Service Name column, click com.amazonaws.ap-southeast-1.ssmmessages. In the VPC section, select Lab VPC. Select the first AZ, then select the Lab Private Subnet subnet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tạo VPC Endpoint</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/_index.vi/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/_index.vi/index.html</guid>
      <description>Tạo VPC Endpoint SSM Chúng ta sẽ tạo 3 interface endpoint yêu cầu bởi Session Manager: Interface endpoint: com.amazonaws.region.ssm com.amazonaws.region.ec2messages com.amazonaws.region.ssmmessages Bạn có thể tham khảo thêm tại đây&#xA;Nội dung: Tạo Endpoint ssm Tạo Endpoint ssmmessages Tạo Endpoint ec2messages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Endpoint ec2messages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.3-endpointec2messages/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1414/example-content/3-accessibilitytoinstances/3.2-private-instance/3.2.2-createvpcendpoint/3.2.2.3-endpointec2messages/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create VPC Endpoint EC2MESSAGES Go to VPC service management console Click Endpoints. Click Create endpoint. At the Create endpoint page. In the Name tag field, enter SSMMESSAGES. In the Service Category section, select AWS Services. In the Service Name section, In the Service category select: AWS services In the field Service Name enter: ec2 then select Service Name: com.amazonaws.ap-southeast-1.ec2messages. In the Service Name column, click com.amazonaws.ap-southeast-1.ec2messages. In the VPC section, select Lab VPC. Select the first AZ, then select the Lab Private Subnet subnet.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>